scoreexchange.com 2019-03-29

# Score Exchange privacy statement

ADAP Solutions Ltd, trading as Score Exchange ("We", "Us", "Our") are committed to protecting information through appropriate controls, being transparent about what data We hold and how We use it, and about respecting Your privacy. "You" ("Your") are Our client to whom We provide services, or are considering entering into an agreement with Us for the provision of Our services.

The rules on processing of personal data are set out in the General Data Protection Regulation (the "GDPR").

This policy sets out the basis on which any Personal Data We collect from You, or that You provide to Us, will be processed by Us.

ADAP Solutions Ltd is a company registered in England under number 5022580, whose registered office and trading address is Unit 20, Highlode Industrial Estate, Stocking Fen Road, Ramsey, Cambridgeshire, PE26 2RB. “We” are the Data Controller.

## What Is The Purpose Of This Privacy Statement?

This privacy statement aims to give you information on how we collect and process your personal data through your use of this website, including any data you may provide through this website when you sign up to our newsletter/purchase a product or service.

You must read this privacy statement together with any other privacy statement we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. 

## Collection And Use Of Your Personal Data

Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. You can find out more about personal data from the [Information Commissioners Office](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/).

In general, you can visit our website without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. If, however, You wish to make a purchase then you enter into a contract with Us for goods/services and You will need to register your full contact details [Title, Name, Billing/Delivery Address, Email Address, Telephone Number/s]. We will store any data that you provide and hold it securely on computer or otherwise.

We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:

  * **Performance Of Contract**

This **** means processing your data where it is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or to take steps at your request before entering into such a contract.

  * **Legitimate Interest**

This means the interest of our business in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service/product and the most secure experience. We make sure we consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative) and your rights before we process your personal data for our legitimate interests. We do not use your personal data for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you, unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law.

## Your Rights In Relation To This Information

If you decide that you no longer wish to receive newsletters, promotional or marketing emails from Us, you have the right to 'opt-out' at any time by adjusting the communication preferences in your account. You may also contact us to manually opt-out.

## Who We Share Your Personal Data With

We may have to share your personal data with the parties set out below for the above-mentioned purposes

  * Pay360 by Capita (processing card payments)
  * Barclays Merchant Services (processing card payments)
  * PalPal (processing payments)

In addition, we also use analytics services provided by Google and Facebook in order to monitor performance of our website.

We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow any third-party to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions. You are advised to read each parties own privacy policy.

## Cookies

A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser which may then store it on your system. Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, use a shopping cart or make card payments. 

If you wish, you can usually adjust your browser so that your computer does not accept cookies. Please remember cookies do not contain confidential information such as your home address, telephone number or credit card details. We do not exchange cookies with any third party websites or external data suppliers.

## Security

Our security measures for storing and disclosing customer details is in accordance the GDPR law so as to prevent unauthorised access to it.

We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information, such as using industry standard encryption for all financial transactions. However, we cannot guarantee the security of any data that you disclose online and we will not be responsible for any breach of security unless this is due to our negligence or wilful default.

We limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

## Data Retention

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

## General

You have the right to make a 'subject access request' as defined under GDPR. Any request should be sent to us at our contact address. We will require two forms of identification to verify your identity and we will process your request upon receipt of this information within the statutory time limits. 

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable admin fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.

This privacy policy was updated on 23 May 2018
